mypengo.com 2010-02-21

# My Pengo

##### privacy policy

##### 1\. What information do we collect?

We collect several different types of information from you. 

###### A. Information collected at registration

We collect personal information when you register with us and when you use our Services. We may combine this information about you with information we obtain from our business partners or other companies. During registration for some of our services, we may require users to give us basic contact information (such as your first and last name, e-mail addresses, and mobile phone number), and demographic information (such as zip code and age). The information requested on the registration form may change from time to time. Although additional demographic information may be requested at the time of registration, only information marked "required" is necessary for registration and utilization of our services. 

We do not accept registrations from persons under the age of eighteen. Our Services are available only to persons who are eighteen years of age and over. If we learn that a user is under the age of eighteen, we will terminate the account and delete the user's information. We will not be liable for any content or advertisements viewed by minor children in violation of the terms of this policy. 

###### B. Information collected through use of the Site and Services

In addition to the specific questions you answer when you register for our content services, we may also collect information, such as their street address, phone number, date of birth. 

We collect system information such as IP addresses (in other words, the location of your computer on the Internet) for system administration, troubleshooting, security, and to examine overall traffic trends. This information, in aggregate form, is recorded for administrative purposes. 

We also may use cookies, a small data file stored on your computer, to customize portions of our Services and Site to your preferences. For example, we may use this cookie to identify you as a registered user of our Services. If you do not allow your browser to accept cookies, please understand that some of the areas or functionality within our Site may be limited. 

Provider allows the user the possibility to interrupt the flow of information received via SMS (Short Message Service). Information received via SMS can be interrupted by sending an SMS message starting with the keyword, i.e. your entry code, followed by a space and then the word STOP or simply sending STOP or STOP ALL. You can send this message to the abbreviated number you used for entry. See for more details the 'unsubscribe' page of the website. 

##### 2\. What do we do with the information we collect?

We use the information we collect from you to do the following: 

  * provide the Services to you,
  * confirm your agreement with us for use of the Services, 
  * bill you for the Services and process other transactions between you and us, 
  * improve our content, 
  * customize certain pages or Services for you, and
  * send you promotional information, and update you about us. 

##### 3\. With whom do we share information? 

Our policy is not to disclosure your personally identifiable information to any third parties, except as follows: 

  * We may disclose such information to third party vendors (e.g., data storage and processing facilities) that we use to assist us in providing our services, subject to similar obligations of confidentiality to those contained in this Privacy Policy. 
  * We share your MDISDN number and your carrier with our aggregator and carrier. 
  * We may disclose information about you to the cellular telephone providers that you select to provide the mobile communications services necessary to access our Services. 
  * We may also disclose information about you as we believe is reasonably necessary to comply with laws, regulations, court or administrative orders, or other governmental authority or to prevent harm to yourself or others. 
  * Finally, we may disclose your personal information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of our stock or assets in the line of business that this privacy policy relates or upon any other corporate reorganization. 

We may also share aggregate demographic and other information regarding use of our Services with third parties for marketing and other purposes. 

##### 4\. Access to your account 

For security reasons, we don’t currently provide users the ability to access or update their accounts on our systems. 

##### 5\. Other websites

Our Site may contain links to other websites. We cannot be responsible for their content or for private information that you may choose to share with them. Please note: any information you release directly to parties who provide services to us, such as any vendors who advertise on our Site or Services, may be subject to different rules of use or disclosure. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing personal information to third parties. 

##### 6\. Security 

Your privacy is important to us and we take reasonable measures to protect the security of the personal information we collect. However, we cannot guarantee absolute security or that your personal information would never be disclosed. In addition, you are responsible for maintaining the security of any passwords of login ids you are provided and for any claims, losses, liabilities or expenses arising out the use of your passwords or ids, whether authorized or not. 

##### 7\. Notice of changes

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy in our sole discretion, and will post any revisions on the Site or through our Services. We encourage you to review this privacy policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and Services will be subject to the then-current privacy policy. If there is a change in this privacy policy that affects your personally identifiable information, we will notify you of the change by e-mail to the address that you have provided to us. At the time of this message, you will be given the option to opt out of this change in information usage by sending a written response message, provided, however that any subsequent use of the Site will subject you to the new privacy policy. 

##### 8\. Contact Information

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact us by mail at: 

2waytraffic mobile usa, inc.   
Concerning Privacy Policy   
1515 Broadway, 12th floor  
New York, NY 10036
